vor.us 2012-09-19

# Fla.vor.us Privacy Tickets - Fla.vor.us

[ ](https://www.bbb.org/online/consumer/cks.aspx?id=1091105132646) [ ](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&url=fla.vor.us&sealid=101) Flavorus has been selling tickets and conducting online transactions for over a decade. We share our customers concern for the protection of their privacy and their personal information. Whether you are simply browsing our site, conducting basic transactions (as a customer or client), or being an involved participant in our content, social network, and marketing, we want you to know what information we are collecting, how we are gathering information, who we are sharing it with, and why. We’ve created this privacy policy to provide our customers, clients and anyone who has given us information through any use of our websites, phone system, and email newsletters a complete description of our practices and your options as a visitor to our site or as a user of our services. 

This privacy policy applies to the practices of [Flavorus](http://www.fla.vor.us/). We work with a variety of third parties who may have their own privacy policies, and we encourage you to seek out information about their practices. Because our offices and servers are in the United States, our privacy policy is drafted according to United States law. Because our website can be accessed from outside of the United States, however, by using our site or services you may engage with businesses located outside of the United States that may be subject to less or more restrictive laws regarding the collection and handling of your information. 

Before using our website, purchasing goods or services through our online or phone system, or opting into our newsletters or media programs, please read this privacy policy thoroughly. By visiting the website or using our services, you are acknowledging and accepting the information gathering and sharing practices detailed below. You can contact us anytime with any questions, concerns, or comments, or to request further information regarding our privacy policy by writing to: 

**Flavorus**  
2808 Elm St.  
Unit 2  
Los Angeles, CA 90065 

You may also submit questions or request further information by emailing us through our help system at: [help@flavorus.com](mailto:help@flavorus.com)

Please note: as our company grows and evolves, we may update this privacy policy so that it remains relevant to our practices. Our privacy policy will always be dated as of the most recent update. Please check back here regularly to ensure that you may be informed of the most current version of this privacy policy. 

###  Index 

Flavorus collects you specific information and general, non-personal information both passively (gathering information you provide) and actively (through technologies such as cookies, web beacons, Google Analytics, etc., and through cooperation with partner businesses and third parties).

####  A. Passive Collection

As a customer or client, or as a participant in our social network and marketing practices, you may provide us with personal contact information such as your name, information (phone number, email address, postal address, etc.), billing information (including your billing address, credit card type and number, etc.) and other information you are prompted to provide. This information may be required to purchase tickets, goods or services, or to participate in various contests, promotions etc. While you have the right to withhold your personal information, doing so may prohibit your ability to conduct transactions, access log into a personal or company account, and so on.

You may also be prompted to provide research or demographic information, such as your age and gender. Demographic information in surveys, as part of a transaction, etc. may be collected, stored and shared, so that we can analyze our business, cater advertising and content to you, and so on.

In addition to information you are prompted to provide, you may also provide us with information, both personal and non-personal, through the use of our interactive zones. By communicating with others through our site or by posting information, you are accepting our information collection and sharing practices as specified in this privacy policy. We do not have control over the dissemination of this information. Post your comments, content, and so on, with careful consideration of how this information may be used and shared on our site and beyond.

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

####  B. Active Collection 

In addition to information that you provide to us, directly or indirectly, we may also collect information (personal and non-personal) through active data gathering practices, using technologies such as cookies and web beacons, and through sharing with our clients, partner businesses, and third parties.

We may use cookies to personalize your experience on the site, track your activity on our site, identify you anonymously, and to gather information about your browser type and language. Cookies, web beacons, Google Analytics, and other technologies can be used to determine referring websites, what kind of searches you are conducting, and other information. You may set your browser security to prohibit us from assigning cookies, however certain features may not be functional without cookies (you may not, for example, be able to log in to a personal client or customer account). Information collected via tracking technologies is not linked to PII.

We may also actively seek out personal and non-personal information from third parties, including partner businesses and advertisers. Flavorus may allow these third parties to incorporate cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information. This information, in general, is used by these outside parties to help focus their advertising or better understand how effective their services are on our site. The information gathering practices of advertisers, partners, and third parties may be subject to their own privacy policies, which we encourage you to seek out and read. Any information we obtain through the collection practices of third parties will be stored, shared, and used in accordance with this privacy policy.

###  2\. Types of Information Collected 

Flavorus, Groovetickets and other partner businesses, clients, and third parties collect two different kinds of information: personal and non-personal.

####  A. Personal 

Flavorus collects personal information, in general, that can verify your identity. This may include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, username and password, etc.

We may also collect billing information to facilitate transactions such as purchasing and selling tickets. This may include your banking account number, credit card number, pin number, expiration date, etc. You have the right to withhold your personal and billing information, however doing so may prohibit your ability to participate in our site or conduct transactions with us or our partners, clients, and third parties.

We may also collect personal, demographic information. This may include your gender, age, and preferences related to the use of our site and services.

Finally, we may collect personal information about your specific activity on the site. This may include which screens you view, how often you visit, how long you are on the site, which advertisements you click through, your purchasing habits, etc.

####  B. Non-Personal 

We may also collect general statistical information not personal to you specifically. Using technologies included (but not limited to) those listed above, and through information sharing with partners, clients, and third parties, we may gather, store, and share information regarding the general use of our sites and services. For example, to monitor our business, and to keep investors, partners, and third parties informed, we may collect and share aggregate information such as average or periodic impressions, advertising statistics, etc.

The non-personal information we collect may be gathered directly, or combined with non-personal information from other websites or outside parties. Non-personal information may also be gathered by cookies and other web technologies, for example, we may collect information about your browser type, language, etc. 

###  3\. Information Sharing Practices 

####  A. Why We Gather Information 

There are a variety of reasons that we may collect information, both personal and non-personal. Information may be gathered to analyze our business, identify you, verify your transactions, customize your experience on the site, for marketing purposes, and so on. Information you provide us may be sent to servers around the United States and around the world. We may also store your information for future use.

Most information is used to facilitate your purchasing experience on Flavorus. This may include fraud protection and identity verification, delivery of your tickets (or other products and services you are obtaining from Flavorus), and support for your customer or client account or transactions. With your consent, we may contact you by telephone, email, postal mail, and other mobile devices to offer support or to advertise on our own behalf or that of partner businesses and third parties. 

We may also use your information to analyze your use of our site, products, services, content and so on. This is to help us customize your experience, develop content, and offer you additional products or services. Additionally, your personal and financial information may be necessary to process refunds, credits, fight fraud and chargebacks,

If you have submitted your personal information in a job application or position with Flavorus or our partner businesses, we may retain your information, regardless of whether or not you are hired. 

**Invite a Friend**  
If you feel that our services could be useful for a third party you know (e.g. your friends or family members etc), you may use our referral service. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 

Our members area also allows for the user to email third parties and to add friends to their network on the site. The site collects third party personal information such as name, email address and phone number. 

**Testimonials**  
We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.  
If you want to remove your personal information that is being displayed on our website under public pages please send your request to help@flavorus.com.

**Widget**  
This site uses the “Share” widget where personal information is collected in the form of the invite-a-friend feature. This feature is used to send a one time invite to the third party email address you entered through the widget. The personal information entered on this widget is subject to the privacy policy of this site.

####  B. Sharing Your information 

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our website or while using our services. Your information may be shared with our business partners and related companies. This may include advertisers, partner businesses, and third parties who provide services for our site. Third party service providers may be used by Flavorus to fulfill orders and process payments. Shipping carriers and marketing parties may also receive your information.

While using Flavorus, you may click through to outside websites operated by third parties. Clicking on an advertisement, for example, may take you to a different website. Our privacy policy does not apply to any third party website, and their collection, sharing, and use of your personal information is subject to their own privacy practices. It is wise to look for privacy policies on any third party website you navigate to. Third party websites that can be navigated to from our site may share with us information they collect independently.

Your information may also be shared with event promoters and staff, including artists and their management, venues, and so on. Flavorus does not plan or produce events, and promoters for events you have purchased tickets for may use your information to contact you, analyze their business practices, etc.

You may opt out of the sharing of your PII with third parties for promotional use by contacting emailing help@flavorus.com or contacting Customer Service by sending a message to the Customer Service profile.

We may also share your information in response to any legal action Flavorus, partner businesses, or third parties may be engaged in. This includes response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, legal process or a request for cooperation from government or law enforcement, or for our own fraud protection. We may also disclose information in the event of a large corporate transaction, such as a merger, sale, or bankruptcy involving Flavorus.

If Flavorus shares information with partner businesses or third parties, your information may be subject to the privacy policies of the outside party. If you are concerned with the handling or use of your personal information by third parties, please consult the privacy policies of those outside organizations. Their policies may differ substantially, and may be subject to the privacy laws of other countries, which may be more or less comprehensive than those in the United States. 

###  4\. Protecting Your Information 

We understand and share concerns about the privacy of information. We have in place both electronic and personnel security measures in place to ensure that your information is protected, and to prevent fraudulent use of your information. Personnel access to your information is limited, and the appropriate information storage security measures as required by law have been implemented. All sensitive information gathered on the site is protected with SSL encryption. 

Flavorus is open to the public, and does not monitor the age of users. In collecting personal information, we do not purposely gather information from children under the age of 13.

By visiting the Flavorus, Groovetickets, or related websites, you are acknowledging and consenting to our information collection, storage, and sharing practices detailed in this privacy policy. You may elect not to provide information when prompted, however doing so may make certain functions, including purchasing, logging into an account, selling, participating in social networking and promotions, etc., may not be available to you.  

You may also adjust the security settings on your browser to block cookies and other web technologies. This may also impair certain functions and services we provide.

If you have an account with us as a customer, client, or member of a social network, you may access, change or update your information by logging into your account or by contacting us through our help system at help@flavorus.com. You may chose to close your account by contacting us through the help system, however after closing the account you may no longer have access to that account’s information, and we may retain information from the original account. We may retain this information for the accuracy of our recordkeeping, accounting, and to assist with fraud protection, fee collection, the enforcement of our terms and conditions, and any other legal action that may be permitted by law. Any information that is shared with third parties may still be stored and shared according to the privacy policies of the third party.

You may opt out of our email newsletters by clicking the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of the newsletter.

You have the right to obtain from us additional information our practices regarding how we share aspects of your personal information with partner businesses and third parties for their use in direct marketing. You may send us a request if you are interested in finding out the following information about our practices: 

**• Which types, or categories, of information we shared to any third party for use in their direct marketing campaigns throughout the previous calendar year.

• Which third parties, including the name and addresses of the individual, business, or organization, who received the information. 

• The products or services marketed by the third party, should the nature of the third party’s business be indecipherable from their name. 

**

Flavorus reserves the right to provide this information to you in a standardized format, not formatted to your specific request. You may send these requests through our help system at [help@flavorus.com](mailto:help@flavorus.com).

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Flavorus is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.   

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact help@flavorus.com or by sending a message to the Customer Service profile. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at:

<http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Effective date of this policy is 08.31.2009.

© Flavorus Inc. All rights reserved.
